<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>about on carla</title><link>https://carlasama.github.io/me/</link><description>Recent content in about on carla</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>pt-br</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 10:13:13 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://carlasama.github.io/me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My Journey as a Developer: Learning, Fun, and Challenges with ADHD</title><link>https://carlasama.github.io/me/blog/first-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 10:13:13 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://carlasama.github.io/me/blog/first-post/</guid><description>Being a developer is a rollercoaster of emotions. Some days, everything clicks, and it feels like I’m on top of the world. Other days, I struggle to keep my focus and find myself overwhelmed by the endless learning and constant deadlines. As someone with ADHD, it’s a journey full of both excitement and challenges.
The Thrill of Learning and Growing One thing that truly excites me about being a developer is the never-ending learning process.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://carlasama.github.io/me/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carlasama.github.io/me/about/</guid><description>About Me I’m a Brazilian-Canadian senior software engineer who loves the idea of destroying all the gatekeeping that exists around software. I’m particularly passionate about making very complex systems sound so simple that a person can only think: “is that all?”
I majored in computer science at University of Campinas and worked on the debugger for Visual Studio at Microsoft for 6 years. I’m based in Vancouver.
I’m currently working on NEVERWAY and a game engine as co-founder at Coldblood Inc.</description></item><item><title>projects</title><link>https://carlasama.github.io/me/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carlasama.github.io/me/projects/</guid><description>Persepolis Built the Persepolis project&amp;rsquo;s front-end with Vue.js and Tailwind CSS, turning UX designs into a responsive website that communicates its mission and social relevance.</description></item></channel></rss>